VARDIS SARTZETAKIS

Ottawa, ON LinkedIn - Portfolio - GitHub

+1 613 413 8417 - elsartz@gmail.com

Profile

Energetic outgoing professional **Business Operations Manager** and **Administrator and Support Director of I.T.** with 15+ years of proven results. Currently, a new graduate of the Full Stack Coding Boot Camp. Experienced UI developer trained in HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript, with additional knowledge of MySQL and Python. Strong team builder, mentor, facilitator and motivator. Superb communication skills and experience in private and public milieus.

Applied Experience

Reference # 4 github.com/elsartz February 2022 - August 2022

Full stack Web Developer at Carleton University

In my repository there are projects where you can have a look of my recent activity working in a group or individually to create web sites or applications on HTML or Node.js. The demands of the boot camp was to make REST API's and also interactive MERN stack single-page applications. Technologies like Dev Tools, Git, ORM, JSON it was necessary to involve in daily bases.

Projects

Tech Blog | GitHub: tech-blog | Heroku

- A socialize application.
- A Javascript application which makes use of several modules from the npm site like express, mysql2, sequelize and handlebars to follow the MVC model, plus bcrypt to encrypt stored passwords.

Quick Forecast | GitHub: Weather-dashboard

- Plan a trip knowing the weather of your destination.
- A Javascript application which uses the openweather API and the moments.js library

README Generator Pro | GitHub: readme-generator-pro

- A creator for readme files of github projects.
- A Node js application which uses the inquirer module.

Professional Experience

Reference # 3 EDMS Dentallytics June 2021 – Nov 2021

System Administrator and Software Developer

- EDMS | DentallyticsTM is a cloud-based Dental Data Analytics software platform for Solo Practices, Dental Groups, and DSOs/DPOs that integrates, correlates, and normalizes data from over two dozen different dental practice management, payroll, and accounting software systems.
- Manage and responsible for ensuring that all the data flows into our system and is processed correctly.
- Check and confirm this process is working correctly.
- Diagnose where and what the issue is and either correct it directly or provide information to the team responsible for fixing the issue so that they can make changes to solve the problem.
- This involves communicating with clients directly via phone, email, or SMS.
- Specific processes and checklists in place that need to be followed as touching directly on either the client's production servers or EDMS production servers.
- Documentation of existing and new processes.
- Assisting in testing and QA on various parts of the EDMS software package.
- Generating reports from client clinic software for comparison to EDMS for other teams.
- Installation of EDMS software on new client clinic servers.

Environment: Thunderbird email client, MobaXterm, WinSCP, AnyDesk, TeamViewer, Remote Desktop, MS Excel, MS Word, Google Drive, Jira, Linux and Windows Server.

Reference # 2 Amazon Warehouse YOW3 Ottawa, On Mai 2021

General Labor

- Started as a worker for general labor and end up organizing the space in the warehouse and
- Managing the time of my colleagues

Reference # 1 Santorini, Greece Restaurant Manager, Owner Apr 2005 – Nov 2020

Business Operations Manager

- Responsible for staff job scheduling, timesheets, expense claims, and annual leave administration
- Managed resource allocations and utilization against project budgets for multiple suppliers
- Performed updates on invoices for the accountant
- Managed social media like Facebook, Instagram, TripAdvisor
- Acquaring SEO experience by creating my shop in Shopify

Environment: Wix, Shopify, Tripadvisor ads, Facebook Pixel, Youtube ads, Canva, Viddyoze

Educational Background

Associated Diploma in	Private College Xini, Athens, Greece
Information Technology	
Stock Market Portfolio	University of Piraeus
Python programming	Aristotelian University of Thessaloniki
Networking Studies Certificate	edX - Western Governors University, USA
(Network Administration)	Coursera
Web Developer Certificate	Carloton University PoetComp
(full stack)	Carleton University BootCamp

Skills and Attributes

Design Tools and Applications Filmora, AutoCad, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, GIMP,

Open Canvas, Corel Painter, MS Paint, Microsoft Visual

Studio, Audacity,

Software Applications Knowledge Pascal, Qbasic, C++, Python, Adobe Acrobat,

Dreamweaver, HTML, CSS, MySql, Oracle,

Office Tools MSOffice, MS Excel, MSWord, MS PowerPoint,

MSOutlook, NeatOffice, MS Project, Keyboarding - 50

wpm, Internet Explorer,

Language Skills Greek native, English business fluency, French basic

Memberships and Associations Woodroffe High School council

Functional Knowledge WHMIS 2015 AIX Safety V3, MOL, Food & Beverage

Hygiene & Safety rules Certificate

Work values

Important values

- You're motivated by work that allows you to help other people, either individually or in small groups.
- You're motivated by work that will lead to a management position.
- You would like to travel and experience different cultures and places.
- You want a calm, peaceful work setting.
- You like work where you can solve problems and decide how things should be done.
- You want work that lets you use your creativity to think up new ways to do things.

Somewhat important values

- It's important to you to get public recognition for the work that you do.
- You would like to work outside all or some of the time.
- You want work that challenges your intellectual capacities.
- You enjoy a workplace with lots of fast-paced activity.
- You like work that lets you persuade or negotiate with others.
- You want work where you get to interact with a team of other people.
- You want to work with responsibilities that change frequently.
- You enjoy work that requires attention to detail and accuracy.